weddingphotography.com.ph 2011-11-30

# Privacy Policy | Wedding Photography Design Philippines

At **Wedding Photography Design (WPD) Blog** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.WeddingPhotography.com.ph and how it is used.

## Log Files

All web servers track basic information about their visitors and like many other web sites, www.WeddingPhotography.com.ph makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes, but is not limited to, internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable and is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, **Wedding Photography Design Blog** use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information and history on which pages the user access or visit, in order to customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to **Wedding Photography Design Blog** and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL

_http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html_

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

## Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology and automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

## Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns and if you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Contact

If you have concerns or questions about this privacy policy, please use the contact form on the site.
